Rebecca Finne

UX Designer - Interaction Design Student

Ambitious interaction design student with a passion for UX and user research. That in my future job, I dream about being able to make a difference, in some way. It could be anything from ending poverty to an individual having an easier everyday life through any product that I have been a part of creating.

Göteborg https://rebecca.finne.se

070-207 93 53 rebecca@finne.se https://www.linkedin.com/in/rebecca-finne

Education

Aug 2018 - Jun 2020 MSc. Interaction Design and Technology, Chalmers University of Technology, Göteborg

Aug 2015 - Jun 2018 BSc. Software Engineering, Chalmers University of Technology, Göteborg

Bachelor's Thesis: Better Together - An Android Application for Increased Physical Activity

The user does different workouts to earn points and every week compete against friends and family. The work focused on creating a good user experience.

Work experience

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019 **Developer Intern**, Spotify

Working with Android Studio, I did bug fixes, tests and developed a feature on the Spotify Lite application. I had one-on-ones with my mentor which taught me tips and tricks on how to easily use the development tools like Android Studio and Github Enterprise.

Dec 2017 - Sep 2019 Meeting leader, Cultural Care Au Pair

Organizing information meetings and interviewing potential au pairs.

Jun 2014 - Jun 2015 Au Pair in the US, Cultural Care Au Pair

I traveled to the USA where I lived in a host family and took care of their child.

For more work experience se my linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/rebecca-finne

Projects

Ongoing Personal website

https://rebecca.finne.se

Sep 2019 - Oct 2019 Save the City from Radiation, Göteborg

School project in collaboration with Universuem. Made a fun and pedagogical game where the players get to learn about the three types of radiation and which materials they can penetrate. Did ideation, paper prototype, user testing and implementation.

Additional merits

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019 Female Student Acceleration Program, Acando

Female Student Acceleration Program is an exclusive network for talented women studying in the fields Information Technology, Management Consulting, Business and Service Design.

Over the period of a year, through workshops, presentations and challenges, Acando provides a set of tools, hands on experience and practical insights for the students to use during their remaining time at the university as well as a kick start to their career

Jul 2018 - Jun 2019 Member of the board in Software Engineering Student Union Board

The board has overall responsibility for the student union, for example, make sure everyone is doing okay, the economics and demand student union meetings.

Nov 2017 - Nov 2018 Vice Chairman in CESA, Computer Education in Southern Africa

Voluntary work to help students in southern Africa get an education with computers. In August 2018 the board of CESA went to South Africa to hand out computers to schools that need them and also fix old and broken computers.

Jan 2016 - Jan 2017 Treasurer for Student Committee at the Software Sngineering Student Union

Planned together with 7 other students three-course dinner for 80-100 people with entertainment, and nightclub events. My position was treasurer which meant I took care of budgets, bookkeeping and responsible for the checkouts during events.

Jan 2009 - May 2014 Swim Coach in Arvika swim team

I had by myself a group of children in the ages 7–12. I coached them once a week, thought them the basics in the four different strokes and had the responsibility during competitions.

Tools Skills Languages

Sketch Wireframing
Figma Prototyping
Adobe Photoshop Interviews
Adobe InDesign Usabilitytesting
Android Studio Java

Android Davelonment

HTML CSS JavaScript

Android Development

References

Will be provided on request.

Swedish - Native English - Advanced